JULIO CASTRO

Senior Software Engineer

julio.castro.dev@gmail.com | +41 76 513 18 64 | Zürich, Switzerland

SUMMARY

Extensive experience in software engineering from startup to large corporate levels. Proven success leading teams in various technologies including Angular, React, Nodejs or Spring Boot, resulting in highly performing, harmonious and cohesive teams with deep technical and business knowledge. Succeeded in applying mathematical and scientific skills to drive and clarify intricate and complex business challenges, resulting in bigger, better and faster achievements.

LANGUAGES AND TECHNOLOGIES

- Languages: Typescript, Java, Python, HTML/CSS, Javascript, SQL
- <u>Technologies:</u> Angular, React, Spring Boot, Nodejs, Nextjs, Cypress
- Other: Domain Driven Design, Clean Arquitecture, Modern Reactivity

EXPERIENCE

Current Senior Software Position

Mar 2019 - Present

- Comment 1.
- Comment 2.
- Comment 3.

Intermediate Senior Software Position

Mar 2019 - Present

- Comment 1.
- · Comment 2.
- · Comment 3.

Intermediate Senior Software Position

Mar 2019 - Present

- Comment 1.
- Comment 2.
- · Comment 3.

Last Senior Software Position

Mar 2019 - Present

- Comment 1.
- Comment 2.
- · Comment 3.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree in Mathematics and Computer Science from the Polytechnic University of Madrid

2017 - 2021

- Achieved an average score of 9/10.
- Awarded for multiple years with academic excellence on behalf of the city of Madrid.

LANGUAGES

- English C1
- Spanish Native
- German A2